[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 4 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "5",
        "7",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 10 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "22",
        "21",
        "24"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 4 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "8",
        "10",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 6 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "3",
        "2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 1 \u00d7 2) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "0",
        "3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 2 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "4",
        "7",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 4 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "2",
        "1",
        "0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 9 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "14",
        "15",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 6 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "9",
        "10",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 5 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "16",
        "15",
        "17"
      ]
    }
]